### IT PROFESSIONAL

Contact				
9310618101				
gulfam.sviim@gmail.com				
Greater Noida Dadri Utter Pradesh (G.B) Nagar-203207				
https://www.linkedin.com/in/gulfam-				
saifi-b86a29166/				
Education				
(2020-2023)				
Bachelor Of Computer				
Application (BCA),				
Asian School of Business (ASB)				
– Noida				
XII <sup>th</sup> From M.B inter college				
(Utter Pradesh Dadri )2019				
X <sup>th</sup> From M.B inter college (Utter				
Pradesh Dadri )2017				
Language				
Hindi, English				
Professional Skills				
Next.js				
React.js				
Deployment				
•••000				
Team leadership				
HTML, CSS, telwind.CSS				
•••000				
SEO O O				

## **Profile**

# Full-Stack Development By (Next.js & React.js)

# Summary

I am a React.js and Next.js Developer and I have worked in A Plus Studio Company as a post of web developer. And I have made full stack website/PWA for A Plus Studio company. and I have done my six months of internship experience from Ghoul-web Solutions as a web developer and I have good knowledge of react.js, next.js. and I have done some project like movies exploring website (full stack) with the help of Next.js, my portfolio by React.js, and Website/PWA for A Plus Studio Company Noida sector-83 A-218-219.

# Work Experience

COMPANY, LOCATION	Experience (Intern)
Ghoul Web Solutions LLP, At Kh No2082, Kathara Road, Dadri, Gautam Buddha Nagar Uttar Pradesh 203207. (https://ghoulweb.com)	Oct 2022 - Apr 2023
A Plus Studio PVT.LTD. Sector-83 A-218 & 219 Utter Pradesh Noida-201305 (https://aplusstudio.in)	Sep 2023 - Jan 2024

## Job Role

• React JS, Next.js, SEO, Deployment.

### Certifications

- Cloud Computing (AWS).
- Personality Development & Corporate Communication.
- MS Office, Excel, Tally ERP.

## Technical skills

- Next.js.
- React.js.
- Mongoose.
- HTML, CSS, telwind.CSS.
- Redux Toolkit.
- Git.
- Context API.

### **Projects**

- Website/PWA for A Plus Studio Company Noida (<a href="https://aplusstudio.in">https://aplusstudio.in</a>)
- My Portfolio (<a href="https://gulfaam.com">https://gulfaam.com</a>)
- Movie Explore web by Next.js, MongoDB, with Next AUTH (https://celebrated-duckanoo-603801.netlify.app/)